gr
gr
gr if the Sánchez mud machine catches her
gr si la pilla la máquina del fango
joo
Sánchez joo
what the [ __ ] is
qué [__]
this the YouTube r good Hispanic arose
esto el YouTube r buen hispano surgió
as an idea of ​​​​Alex molón in response to
como idea de Alex molón en respuesta a
complaints about the increasingly worse rew
las quejas por las cada vez peores rew
of YouTube itself and the almost scarce
de la propia YouTube y la casi escasa
Hispanic representation that there was in
representación hispana que había en
these enjoying several editions
estos gozando esta de varias ediciones
of which we can highlight those of
de las cuales podemos Resaltar las de
2019 and 2020 and from there onwards lowering its
2019 y 2020 y ahí en adelante bajando su
popularity due to the little novelty that
popularidad por la escasa novedad que
its memes brought, mostly Spanish,
traían sus memes en su mayoría españoles
worse than its dubbing, which is that of
más malos que su doblaje que es eso de
pachur and finally increasingly
pachur y fin financiamiento cada vez más
scarce financing since YouTubers
escaso ya que a los youtubers les
love to appear without contributing anything but
encanta aparecer sin aportar nada pero
who can blame them since those who
quién puede culparlos ya que los que si
did pay only appeared for a few seconds on
pagaban solo aparecían pocos segundos en
screen if they weren't Auron or El Rubius,
pantalla si no eran auron o El Rubius
not to mention that they did not let him
esto sin mencionar que no le dejaron
have the exclusive greev like the grandmother
tener la exclusiva greev como la abuela
in her building all this marking the
en su edificio todo esto marcando el
inevitable success and fall of YouTube rin
Inevitable éxito y caída del YouTube rin
Hispanic of Alex
hispano de Alex
molón damn, we have to do something
molón ostia habrá que hae algo
no If I had money If I had money
no Si tuviera dinero Si tuviera dinero
[Music]
[Música]
Let's go
Vámonos
Javi What is that  to sell Here it comes
Javi Qué es eso de vender Aquí se viene
cry too from home here we hold with
llorad too de casa aquí se holdea con
balls here we don't sell anything until you
[__] aquí no se vende nada hasta que
have millions in your wallet imbecile
no tengas millones en la cartera imbécil
to hold go hold your cousin from
a holdear va holdea tu prima la de
Murcia
murcia
[Music]
[Música]
And me what And me that [ __ ] keep going
Y yo qué Y yo que que gilipolla tira
go that face that has
para adelante anda la cara esa que tiene
for a chicken sandwich
para un sándwich de pollo
[Music]
[Música]
It's been a while since I heard from you I was
hace rato que no sé nada de ti estaba
with someone but now I'm FREE pua to
con alguien pero ya estoy FR pua para
revive seen time I haven't gone out in a while
revivir vio tiempo no salgo hace tiempo
you tell me where are you it's been a while since I
tú dime dónde
heard from
estás que ha rato que no sé nada
you with someone but now I'm free to
ti con alguien pero ya estoy free para
revive time I haven't gone out in a
revivir tiempo no sal hace
while daddy we don't waste we park and
tiempo papi no perdemos nos parqueamos y
turn it on for the dry we drink and
lo prendemos para la seca bebemos y
when we get drunk we put on a reggaeton
cuando nos emborrachamos una de regetón
and we go where we can't
ponemos y nos vamos a donde no podamos
love we can't
querer no podamos
eat it's a challenge I haven't heard from you I
comer hace reto que no sé nada de ti
was with someone but now I'm F it's
estaba con alguien pero ya estoy F
hard to
cuesta para
revive Another year being a woman how
revivir Un año más siendo mujer cómo
time flies spectacular [ __ ]
pasa el tiempo espectacular [__]
Ah what in the host This has been the [ __ ]
Ah qué en la [__] Este ha sido el [__]
Javi uncle [ __ ]
Javi tío cabrón
[Music]
[Música]
this year there have been many altercations it has been
este año han pasado muchos altercados se
done  longer than IB with the Camino
ha hecho más largo que IB con el camino
de Santiago we went live this year
de Santiago entramos en directo este año
the news has been a riot one was
las noticias han sido un alboroto uno
going for an interview until
iba para una entrevista hasta que lo
Pablo Moto called him things got
llamó Pablo moto la cosa se quedó
messed up anger I didn't have an anger of
revuelta bronca no tenía un enfado de
another level much less than the one
otro nivel mucho menos que el que tenía
the mae had with the
la mae con el
churumbel again champion if he catches you he'll
churumbel otra vez campeón si te pilla
break your nose his people don't have a
te rompe la nariz los suyos no tien
name that Lucas from Andy Luc from that
nombre que Lucas de Andy luc de ese
man I loved it when novita
hombre Me encantaba cuando novita
tried to flirt with sisuca it freaked me out a
intentaba lig con sisuca lo flipaba un
lot Although I started to find it less
montón Aunque yao empezo a hacerme menos
funny when they saw the cloth rejón I hope
gracia cuando veían la tela rejón Ojalá
that in 2025 politicians lose their
que en 2025 a los políticos le quiten el
salaries and they look for their own way and if they
sueldo y se busquen la vida y si
need help from the people they ask for it polif
necesitan ayuda del pueblo la pida polif
with
con
hispano banano and v you against well the
hispano banano y v tú contra bien la
true dick I'll bust you don't get carried away
verada picha te reviento no te agas
tanda zer huello we're in the same hole
tanda zer huello estamos en el mismo pzo
dick
picha
[Music] take
[Música]
advantage I wanted to show you what
aprovecha os quería enseñar qué es lo
comes home because today Pablo
que os llega a casa pues hoy a Pablo le
felt like watching a video of dros So I
ha apetecido ver un vídeo de dros Así
shaved it and made you record for  m what
que lo rapé e hice que grabas para m
you're going to see below is not a top they
vas a ver a continuación no es un top
are extremely delicious recipes
son recetas sumamente deliciosas por
by an influencer who shows her
parte de una influencer que demuestra su
love through
amor
cooking this person raises all kinds
cocinando esta persona levanta todo tipo
of passions and thanks to her
de pasiones y gracias a sus
brainless haters she became a
descerebrados haters se volvió toda una
viral internet sensation with millions
sensación viral de internet con millones
of followers and many many fans her
de Seguidores y muchos muchos fans su
name is rorro and she's going to give you a lot to
nombre es rorro y te va a dar mucho en
think about today before going to
qué pensar hoy antes de ir a
dinner dros has spoken to you and I wish you Bon
cenar te ha hablado dros y te deseo Buen
appetit my youtuber friends what can I say about
provecho amigos youtubers qué decir de
you
vosotros
eh especially in these last months thank you thank you
eh sobre todo en estos últimos meses
for
daros las gracias las gracias por
your work and also thank you for
vuestra labor y también las gracias por
your defense we have felt very
vuestra defensa os hemos sentido muy
close we have felt very close
cerca os hemos sentido muy hermanados
to us that we are another medium that is
con nosotros que somos otro medio que
television but we really
somos la televisión pero de verdad os
follow you a lot and from here thank you for
seguimos mucho y desde aquí agradeceros
the good I have become a fan of many
lo bueno yo me he vuelto fan de muchos
eh I already was I have discovered
eh yo ya lo era yo He descubierto a
many as a result of this controversy that you all
muchos a raíz de esta polémica que todos
know and the truth is that it does not
conocéis y la verdad es que no me
surprise me that you have so many followers
extraña que tengáis tantos seguidores
because there are great communicators
porque hay grandísimos comunicadores
some of course and I knew them others
algunos por supuesto y los conocía otros
have joined and to all of you to all of you I
se han incorporado y a todos a todos yo
send you a huge hug you have been
os mando un abrazo enorme habéis sido
a force  of first gravity in a
una fuerza de primera gravedad en una
rather delicate situation we have
situación bastante delicada hemos
felt your total support
sentido vuestro apoyo total
regardless of whether we think the same or not that
prescindiendo de que pensemos o no lo
it does not matter support for
mismo que eso da igual un apoyo a la
freedom we are delighted you have us at
libertad estamos encantados nos tenéis a
your disposal the
vuestra disposición el ejército
millennial army that many of you
milenario que muchos de vosotros ya
were already millennials so nothing a
erais milenarios así que nada un beso
big kiss to all and let's hope to see you
muy fuerte para todos y esperemos verlos
soon also see if we get together one
pronto también ver si nos juntamos un
day happy new
día feliz
year Welcome to the bonfire where we
año Bienvenidos a la hoguera donde
burn doubts esperanzaz
quemamos dudas esperanz
[Music]
[Música]
auron we have images for you est I already
auron tenemos imágenes para ti est ya la
saw this situation it is here this I saw it I saw
vi esta situación ya está esta la vi la
oysters this is new this I already
vi ostras esta es nueva esta ya me
found out And this is the milk this is all I
enteré Y esta es la leche esto es todo
see that these shocking images do not
veo que estas impactantes imágenes no te
catch you by surprise it is not the dick if I
pillan por sorpresa no ra la [__] si te
tell you the
digo la
[Music]
[Música]
truth I have decided to participate in
verdad me he propuesto participar en
this reality
este reality
[Music]
[Música]
advent that's
avent ese eres
you Flex your temptation has come to see you
tú Flex tu tentación ha venido a verte
[ __ ] what an [ __ ] I haven't done I haven't
[__] qué cabrón Yo no hecho yo no he
done anything eh guys don't pay attention to
hecho nada eh chicos no hagáis caso a
these images they are surely
estas imágenes seguro que están
manipulated we have very heavy images
manipuladas tenemos imágenes muy heavies
for
para
you out of the [ __ ] Take that away that is an [ __ ] the
ti fuera [__] Quita eso que es cabrón la
sharpener's position what a scandal
postura del afilador qué escándalo
[Music]
[Música]
We have breaking news. We have
tenemos una noticia de última hora nos
just been informed that Juan Guarnizo has
acaban de comunicar que Juan guarnizo ha
been caught with the Only Fans actress
sido pillado con la actriz de only fans
Milica. Do you know how we found out?
milica sabéis cómo nos hemos enterado
Milica uploaded some Stories to her
milica ha subido unas Stories a su
Instagram and there you could see that the
Instagram y ahí se ha podido ver que la
bed in the photo she uploaded belonged
cama de la foto que ha subido pertenecía
to Juan Guarnizo's bed and that
a la cama de Juan guarnizo y que se veía
the dog could be seen and the dog's back
a la perrita y el lomo de la perrita
also belonged to Juan Guarnizo's dog.
también era de la perrita de Juan
Neither of them has
guarnizo todavía ninguno de los dos ha
wanted to acknowledge their story yet, but
querido reconocer su historia pero lo
what we can say from here is that
que sí podemos decir desde aquí es que
Juan Guarnizo, my friend, you are in [ __ ]
Juan guarnizo amigo estás en el [__]
Prime. The gossip, the gossip is over
Prime el salseo el salseo ha terminado
with me. I'm telling you, I can't take it anymore. I can't
conmigo ya os lo digo no puedo más no
take it anymore. Among so many
puedo más entre tantas muestras
creepy displays of love and sugar, I
espeluznantes de amor y de azúcar es que
've covered everything, everything, weddings, here's
he cubierto de todo de todo bodas aquí
the most recent one, not the one with Isabel
tenéis la más reciente no la de Isabel
Antoja with Bertin Osborne, one of the
antoja con Bertin osborne una de las
weddings of the year, another romantic moment, or
bodas del año otro momento romántico o
not, that of Bárbara Rey with Yoda. Although
no el de Bárbara Rey con yoda Aunque yo
if I were him, it would be Jordi Puyol or Yoda. Oh,
si fuera él es Jordi Puyol o es yoda Ah
no, I'm saying, it's Jordi.  Puyol be
no vale digo es que si es Jordi Puyol
careful because you're going to get blackmailed you're
cuidado cuidado porque te va a caer te
going to get blackmailed no no Well
va a caer un buen chantaje no no Bueno
then Hey, between them, they
pues Oye entre ellos entre ellos se
understand each other Hey, finally I'm
entienden Oye por fin me alegro
so glad Terelu has found the
muchísimo terelu ha encontrado después
man of her life after 9 years without her it's because we've
de 9 años sin el hombre de su vida es
given so much news, so much
que hemos dado tantas noticias tantas
news, some of it terrifying
noticias algunas de ellas espeluznantes
horí
horí por
please it's that this year's gossip,
favor es que lo del salseo de este año
as they always say, pay attention because
como siempre dicen mucha atención porque
reality ends up surpassing fiction,
la realidad termina superando la ficción
what will 2025 bring us?
qué nos deparará
What are you doing? Close the door
2025 Qué haces Cierra la puerta
then The news is confirmed And if this
pues Se confirma la noticia Y si esta no
isn't the news of the year, let Saint Pancras come down
es la noticia del año que baje San
and tell me about Greev and Sofía
Pancracio y me lo diga de greev y Sofía
fitness, they're together, many of you
fitness están juntos muchos de vosotros
letting yourselves be carried away by the most
dejándose llevar por la vena más
patriarchal vein. You'll wonder How
patriarcal Se preguntará Cómo habrá
could the guy from Murcia have hit on the
podido el murciano tirarle la caña a la
nag? But this time it wasn't the cane, it
jamelga Pero esta vez no ha sido la caña
was the inverted pineapple in the
ha sido la piña invertida en el carro
Mercadona cart, that flirting technique that
del mercadona esa técnica de ligoteo que
's wreaking havoc on me and be the
está haciendo estragos por and sea la
mother who gave birth to me and I'm so alone in my
madre que me parió y yo tan solo en mi
theater that
teatro que el
am this year almost all the
am este año lo han dejado casi todas las
couples on Twitch have left  Chavi tell me that you and I are
parejas de Twitch chavi dime que tú y yo
never going to separate Of course
no nos vamos a separar nunca Pues claro
not Cari what's more I'm going to tell you something
que no Cari es más te voy a decir algo
with
con amor
cushioning love Oh what I've suffered I
amortiguador Ay lo que he sufrido yo
whisper your mouth doesn't stop we want to say that
surra tu boca no para queremos decir que
we are not together as a couple was never
no estamos juntos como pareja nunca fue
unfaithful there was never a third person to me
infiel nunca hubo una tercera persona me
that people don't believe that people
que la gente no se cre que las personas
change Ar and I made the
camb Ar y yo hace semanas tomamos la
decision to get divorced weeks ago bu we've
decisión de divorciarnos bu hace un
not been
tiempo que ya no estamos
together for a while now I screwed up but at least not He
juntos yo la [__] pero por lo menos no
was unfaithful If you understand me Carlos and I
Fu infiel Si me entiendes Carlos y yo lo
broke up three weeks ago we're not
hemos dejado hace ya tres semanas que no
together okay we're not together anymore
estamos juntos vale ya no estamos juntos
dad and mom have separated okay Maria
papá y mamá se han separados vale María
is in another stage of life don't let
se encuentra en otra etapa de vida que
anyone tell you that nothing is forever I
nadie os diga que nada es para siempre
also had to say what I
tenía también como que decir lo que
felt and what was happening to me and another thing is to
sentía y lo que me pasaba y otra cosa es
rip out a heart cirl and [ __ ] on your
arrancar un corazón cirle y cagarte en
[ __ ] I haven't put horns in revenge on
[__] yo no he puesto cuernos en venganza
anyone horns are horns Yes
a nadie unos cuernos son unos cuernos Sí
obviously like I said you know what
evidentemente en plan yo dije sabes qué
this has to end Yes or yes blah blah
esto tiene que acabar Sí o sí bla bla
blah your mouth doesn't stop damage the bell
bla tu boca no para dañe la campana
drama that doesn't heal gossip And whisper your echo
drama que no sana chisme Y susur tu eco
is absurd I go up  to the future you fall into
es absurdo yo subo al futuro caes en
your mouth does not stop bathing the bell that
los tu boca no para bañ la campana que
I do not
no s
profess any religion Although my
no profeso ninguna religión Aunque mis
actions may be considered a
acciones puedan ser consideradas un
sin or my words are not true I do
pecado o mis palabras no sean verdaderas
not fear God but I have love and
no temo a Dios pero tengo amor y
compassion for my fellow men Daniel
compasión por mis semejantes Daniel
Sancho do you want to know the profile of
Sancho quieres conocer el perfil de
Daniel Sancho and Edwin Arrieta tour
Daniel Sancho y Edwin Arrieta recorrer
with me the island of Copá the
conmigo la isla de copá el escenario del
crime scene the places where the
crimen los lugares donde restos de la
victim's remains know the ins and outs of the
víctima conocer los entresijos del
trial the internal struggles in the
juicio las luchas intestinas en los
media and many other
medios de comunicación y muchas otras
things that have never been told come
cosas que nunca se han contado ven
with me rq in the crazy chest r for
conmigoo rq en el pecho loco r para el
2024 with love r to 2025 and says
2024 con cariño r to 2025 y dice
[Music]
[Música]
we are already heavyweights like ma
ya somos pesos pesados como la ma
singing to my gypsy like the churumbel
cantándole a mi gitana como el churumbel
going around the world like hate does it
dando vueltas al mundo como hace el hate
only exists on the internet I'm still
solo existe en internet aún ando
looking for love like the vellido I wanted
buscando el amor como el vellido quería
like going the kilol to give it your last name
como ir el kilol a ponerle tu apellido
but this year has been somewhat atypical since I
pero este año ha sido algo atípico desde
saw va and his physical change dreaming of
que vi va y su cambio físico soñando con
the big house light chocas fighting for my
el casoplon light chocas luchando por mi
sanctuary Fran cuesta  I am the revelation
santuario Fran cuesta soy la revelación
as a metric remember dad georgio
como métrica recuerda el papá georgio
looks down on us
nos Mira desde arriba
internet users my hearts
internautas corazones míos
my
mi
life I wish you all a happy new year
vida os deseo un feliz año nuevo para
and all your
todos vosotros y para todas vuestras
family may we have good health and
familia que tengamos mucha salud y nos
see you soon a big kiss
vemos pronto un besazo os
I love you we love you and we send you
quiero te amamos y te mandamos
many See you soon
muchos Hasta pronto
so it feels like I can even make that
so it feels like I can even make that
Choice Now and and Pick my Last moment
Choice Now and and Pick my Last moment
as My Rock at the
as My Rock at the
bottom I can make a new one and make a
bottom I can make a new one and make a
whole New Love That's My
whole New Love That's My
[Music]
[Música]
Choice for
Choice for
devil this big ass has a really
[__] esta culona tiene una teta bien
badass tit I don't know what I'm gonna do I wanna
cabrona Yo no sé qué voy a hacer quiero
give her anal sex sex sex sex
darle sexo anal sexo sex sex
[Music]
[Música]
sex Come on toto Come on move toto Come mu to
sex Dale toto Dale mueve toto Dale mu to
Come on yo bu a crown but not for so much
Dale to yo bu una corona pero no para
people move that ass Come on
tanto gente muéveme ese culo Dale dale
move that ass Come on move to Come on move to up down
mueve ese culo Dale mueve to Dale mueve
Come on mother I'm coming good that she
Dale madre me estoy viniendo buena que
is really rich that she has an
está bien rica que tiene un culo unas
incredible ass My God Saint and they just
increíbl Dios mío Santo y apenas me
fined me yesterday
funaron ayer
[ __ ] but this What is it that the
cabrón pero esto Qué es que caiga ya el
[Music]
[Música]
meteorite falls now let's go  See ivai ivai you
meteorito vamos a ver ivai ivai tú me
're listening to me you're not fat man
estás escuchando no estás gordo tío
you're potbellied I mean you have a belly that you
estás panzón O sea tienes una panza que
look like the belly I don't know what you want me to
pareces el panzas no sé que quieres que
tell you you have the opportunity you have
te diga tienes la oportunidad tienes
money you have time that you have to
dinero tienes tiempo que tienes que
be all the [ __ ] working and
estar todo el put trabajando and
doing events I'm the best I'm the
haciendo eventos soy el mejor soy el
best You're a fat man look at yourself Look at that you see that over there that's
mejor Eres un gordo tío mírate Mira eso
a
eso de ahí lo ves eso eso es un tío
muscular man Compared to you Fran man don't get in line
cachas Comparado contigo Fran tío no te
don't get in line with the poor bull do you
cueles no te cueles con el pobre toro me
understand me No you
entiendes No tú me
understand me you try you make a mistake you
entiendes lo intentas te equivocas te
get up
levantas
[Music] Don't Take [ __ ] got no Love the and hate show up and [Music] [Applause] [
[Música]
[Music] make Oh [Applause] [Music] let's
[Música]
see lights
a ver luces
gentlemen many consider them the kings
señores muchos los consideran los reyes
of the European forests a symbol of
de los bosques europeos un símbolo de la
masculinity and
masculinidad y la
[Music]
[Música]
strength but their history
fuerza pero su histor
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
of my fears
de mis miedos
that everyone is
que está todo el mundo
with me who  listen to the moon one two
conmigo que se escuche la luna un dos
three
tres
it's from Colombia and Puerto Rico wc and
está desde Colombia y Puerto Rico wc y
Arcángel from this moment that I
Arcángel a partir de este momento que os
'm announcing it to you, Juna is no longer
lo estoy anunciando juna deja de ser
president of Science because in the end it
presidenta de Science porque al final
's something personal Between him and I, she's not
pues es algo personal Entre él y yo no s
president of sancia Parral Parral son
presidenta de sancia Parral Parral hijoa
Kings leag Z Z Z Z or rather a serious question, do
Kings leag Z Z Z Z o sea pregunta seria
any of you watch the Kings
alguno de vosotros ve la Kings
[Music]
[Música]
le Well, look at my last game, not
le Pues mira mi último partido de no
Kinsley but Queens law of girls like
kinsley sino Queens ley de chicas como
you to whom we are giving a lot of
tú a la que estamos dando bastante
visibility in women's soccer, I had
visibilidad en el fútbol femenino tuve
55,000 people only on my channel until it came
55000 personas solo en mi canal hasta
out and on the scene for whatever reason she was
que no ha salido y de escena por lo que
afraid to give her opinion
sea le dio miedo a dar su opinión
[Music]
[Música]
How crazy a long time ago, man, that tournament
Qué locura hace tiempo tío ese torneo
is H repeated the last
est H repetido la última
game this is history history I don't see
partida esto es histor histor no veo
Juan I don't see it, he's never been to Salamanca
Juan no veo nunca ha ido a Salamanca
but I will go man and someday we'll see each other
pero iré tío y algún día nos vemos
Thanks for all the support and the car, you're welcome
Gracias por todo el apoyo y el car de
Juan, that's what we're here for, man, [ __ ] great
nada Juan para eso estamos tío [__]
so that later you say that
madre para que luego digáis que la skin
Rubius's skin looks like him Look at the height
de Rubius se parece a él Mirad la altura
Rubius is taller than me and look
Rubius es más alto que yo y Mirad
[Music]
[Música]
Here Ah It's his father's death is that
aquí Ah Es muer de su padre es que
we came to have a good time peñ
venimos a pasarlo bien peñ
Peña 37 and I have apart from the trophy the
Peña 37 y tengo aparte del trofeo la
bandana child in need of attention and that's it It's
bandana niño necesitado de atención y ya
okay guys control your
está No pasa nada chicos controla tus
words crack I'm not going through there anymore I'm
palabras crack por ahí ya no paso por
not going through there eh I'm not going through there
ahí ya no paso eh Por ahí sí que no paso
Calm down a little
Cálmate un poquito
[Music]
[Música]
If these awards represent a huge problem
si estos premios suponen un problema muy
for the creators, I feel
grande para los creadores a mí me sabe
really bad having that live show, I'm telling you, it
muy mal tener ese directo os lo digo de
really doesn't compensate for all the effort that
verdad no compensa todo el esfuerzo que
the project takes and all the money that
lleva el proyecto y todo el dinero que
I have invested in the slam awards, okay.
yo he invertido en los premios slam vale
But if on top of that, there are creators who
Pero si además de eso hay creadores que
say Look, I don't want to be awarded
dicen Mira yo no quiero ser premiado a
anything, I'm left in a position of
nada yo ahí me quedo en una posición de
really being worth the effort I
realmente merece la pena el esfuerzo que
'm making, the awards
estoy haciendo es que los premios
inevitably generate a lot of
generan de una manera Inevitable mucha
confrontation between communities, the
confrontación entre comunidades las
communities fight because they defend
comunidades se pelean porque defienden a
their streamer, I've already seen that
su streamer ya ya vi que comenzaron a
some streamers from the Atam started to come out and
salir algunos streamers de la atam a
say I'm not going to go, it's a total test,
decir yo no voy a ir es una prueba total
if it goes well and there's no toxicity, it's
si sale bien y no hay toxicidad
impossible, well, I'm not going to go like to the
imposible bueno no voy a ir tipo a los
eland because it's also a trip
eland porque también es un viaje
incredible high jerk but yes surely
increíble alta paja pero sí seguramente
next year we're going to go to the evening
el año que viene vamos a ir a la velada
I'm not at all in agreement
yo no estoy en lo absoluto de acuerdo
with this type of dynamics and this
con este tipo de de dinámicas y este
type of things Hey this is already
tipo de cosas Oye esto ya me está me Me
worrying me to the point of speaking with you
está preocupando al nivel de hablar con
in private no and saying quakiti what has
en privado no y decir quakiti qué ha
happened and well between one thing and another
pasado y bueno entre unas cosas y otras
we have been talking about the
hemos estado hablando de la
female representation in the awards
representación femenina en los premios
not the female representation Obviously
no la representación femenina Obviamente
the problem is the
el problema es la representación
female representation But what I can't make
femenina Pero yo lo que no puedo hacer
is an investment as large as the one made
es una inversión tan grande como hecho
the previous three years this year the
los tres anteriores años este año los es
Lance will do yes Well basically
Lance harán si Pues básicamente se
the expenses can be covered with the
pueden cubrir los gastos con los
income then compete in a
ingresos a continuación competir en un
tug of war with a rope that has
tira y afloja con una cuerda que tiene
a red flag in the center the winner is
una bandera Roja en el centro ganan
whoever clicks more than on the flag
quienes den más clics que en la bandera
towards their side of the bridge let the
hacia su lado del puente que comience el
game begin Go damn Go it
juego Dale
's my anus it's mine it's
Dale es mi ano es mio es
mine the can
mio la can
[Music]
[Música]
of let's see the fall fast keep giving keep
de a ver la caída ráp sigue dando sigue
giving keep
dando
sucking it the computer security of
chuparla la seguridad informática de
all the participants of the
todos los participantes del juego del
squid game 3 is now vulnerable right now I
calamar 3 está ahora mismo vulnerable o
mean we were winning and it
sea íbamos ganando nosotros y ha hecho
flopped and they threw us
flop y nos han tirado
no
no
decar  listen Agustín stop crying or
decar escucha Agustín deja de llorar o
start hacking channels dude it's enough
empiez a hackar canales tío ya está bien
that you don't hang up on me
que no me cuelgues
[Music]
[Música]
that Fran has been hacked show me a
que han hackeado a a Fran me enseñas un
pixel of the lawsuit even if it
pixxel de la demanda aunque
's just a little bit of a tit at least it's that
sea un cachito de teta por lo menos sea
you're
que te lo estás inventando
completely making it up that B theory that I'm
completamente esa B teoría que me la
making it up Because you told me you
estoy inventando Porque me dijiste que
had proof proof of what no this one I
tenías pruebas pruebas de qué no este me
refuse to show it And who does he
resero a mostrarlas Y a quién se la pasa
show it to I refuse I refuse now they
a mostrar me resero me resero ahora bien
have something to reproach that contract
tienen algo que reprochar ese contrato
doesn't prevent you from reporting if something has been done to you it
no te impide denunciar si te han hecho
prevents because reporting it means
algo impide porque denunciarlo supone
telling a lawyer what you have signed
contarle a un abogado lo que has firmado
and a third party cannot be a part of
y un tercero no puede ser partícipe de
that contract it is that it is in the
ese contrato es que lo pone en el propio
contract itself I refuse I refuse you reserve what I
contrato me resero me resero te reservas
reserve the comments the
el qué me resero los comentarios la
truth But you reserve what Or
verdad Pero te reservas el qué O para
what for is it that I don't
qué es que no lo
understand eno review says about you that you
entiendo eno review dice de ti que todo
are constantly contacting girls on
el tiempo estás contactando chicas por
Instagram that you are no saint and
Instagram que tú no eres ningún santo y
that you spend your time Well, flirtatious
que tú te la pasas Pues de coqueto
trying to meet girls on
tratando de quedar con chicas por
Instagram  and show the evidence of
Instagram lo and muestra las pruebas de
that right now the evidence is my
eso ahora mismo las pruebas son mi
testimony Look Hey ric I have something
testimonio Mira Oye ric tengo una cosita
here for you, here, here eat
aquí para ti
it You just have to open your
toma toma cómetelo Solo tienes que abrir
mouth open your mouth Abela what we are
la boquita abre la boca abela que lo que
going to talk about here is not Pambi
vamos a hablar tú y yo aquí no es pambi
what we are going to talk about here is
lo que vamos a hablar tú y yo aquí es
our personal topic a few moments
nuestro tema personal unos momentos
later don't change the subject is that the
después que no me cambies de tema es que
topic has always been p the question I
el tema sipre ha sido p la pregunta que
'm asking I don't want to talk to
estoy haciendo No quiero hablar más con
Javi anymore he's doing the danas of
Javi está haciendo la de danas de
diverting the topic from Pambi I'm not interested in
desviar el tema de pambi no me interesa
talking about anything that isn't zto do you measure
hablar de algo que no sea zto te mide
how much do you measure me
que cuánto me mide Sé que no quieres
I know you don't want to answer because you know that I've seen your [ __ ] have you seen my [ __ ] Yes have you seen my dick what have you seen my dick Ah V I'll tell you m blah blah blah same restraining order they realize that we are in
alejamiento se dan cuenta que estamos en
the rewind
el rewind
the discussion went too far I don't
la tertulia llegó bastante lejos a mí no
care about anything I suck a whole egg
me importa nada me chupo todo un huevo
I want my Esla nothing more
Yo quiero mi Esla nada más
Spanish Serene has died eh what the [ __ ]
españoles serene ha muerto eh qué [__]
happened to Serene where the [ __ ] is
ha pasado con serene dónde [__] está
Serene and I saw this from the
serene y esto lo he visto por los
comments  serene has been practically two weeks
comentarios serene lleva dos semanas
Without giving any signs of life
prácticamente Sin dar señales de vida
What did Willy Rex do, what game did he play, do you
Qué hizo Willy Rex qué juego
authorize the game did Willy Rex do,
hizo autorizas aé juego hizo Willy Rex
what game did he play
qué juego hizo
sometimes now
veces ya
eh it doesn't matter, I mean, close directly and
eh da igual o sea cer directo y ya os
I'll tell you why I can't find the car, I
contaré porque no encuentro el coche o
mean
sea
[Music]
[Música]
e
e
Opa chicken crazy chicken chicken crazy chicken Crazy Chicken chicken
Opa pollo pollo loco pollo pollo loco
crazy chicken chicken crazy
Pollo Loco pollo pollo loco pollo pollo
chicken Austria graphics eh graphics Let's go I would buy it David David tell me sister can you please come out for me the olives I'm going Thank you Thank you brother can you please come out for me water water water water also water also here you thank you brother put some chips and lastly the chips chips chips chips lastly now
las patatitas patatitas fritas patatitas
come on let's go with
fritas lo último ya ya venga vamos con
the chips thank you brother thank you And
las patatitas gracias hermano gracias Y
lastly really a blanket please
a lo último de verdad una manta porfa
I'm a little cold no a
que tengo un poquito de frío no una una
blanket no now now her have a little
manta ya no ya ya her tiene un poquito
compassion that I broke my ligament it's
de compasión que me roto el ligamento es
the bone of the
el heso de la
leg also it's true And you think
pierna tamb es verdad Y vos te pensas
that in the Stream of marvels I don't
que en el Stream de maravilla yo no te
recommend you
recomiendo a vos
well room exit exit we are in
bueno sala salida salida estamos en
class  religion Thank you very much Happy New
clase de religión Muchas gracias Feliz
Year, may they give you many things The
año que os regalen muchas cosas Los
Kings You know here your trusted war reporters,
Reyes Ya sabéis aquí vuestro reporteros
we'll see you gentlemen, if we continue like this this won't
vemos señores como sigamos así esto no
work, eh the
funciona eh llega la
[Music]
[Música]
director arrives 4
directora 4
million that
millones
a boy told me
de es que un chico me ha dicho
that 1000
que 1000
euros calm down calm down don't
eur tranquilos tranquilos que no cunda
panic it was a mistake Hello, we come
el pánico ha sido un error Hola venimos
from the future and we just won the
del futuro y acabamos de ganar las
2025 elections and for that we are going to
elecciones de 2025 y para eso os vamos a
introduce you to our official team
presentar a nuestra plantilla oficial
that will govern Spain in 2025, let's
que va a gobernar España en este 2025
go with her and give way to the prime
vamos con ella y damos paso a la primera
minister
ministra
Hello, I am the minister of defense
Hola Soy la ministra de defensa
Oh, here we go, let's
Ah
give way to the second
toma damos paso al segundo
minister, fantastic fans from all over Spain,
ministro fans fantásticos de todo España
I am the minister of health if you have
yo soy el ministro de sanidad si tienes
a type of illness then sell my
un tipo de enfermedad pues venta mi
laboratory and I will treat you with my
laboratorio y te voy a tratar con mi
health care, do you want my treatment then
sanidad quieres mi tratamiento pues
look for me and I will treat you, I can
Búscame y yo te voy a tratar te puede
cure you of any type of
curar cualquier tipo de
illness, bye and we give way to the third
enfermedad chao y damos paso al tercer
minister, I am dav scorpion and I am the
ministro yo soy dav escorpion y soy
minister of sport, always scorpion and
ministro de deporte siempre escorpión y
always all scorpions because I really
siempre toos escorpiones porque que me
like a bug that I really like,
gusta mucho un [__] que me gusta mucho
graas that  develop the techniques of the
graas eso desarrollar las técnicas del
Scorpion scorpion we give way to the
Escorpión escorpion damos paso a la
fourth minister Hello, I'm Taira and I'm
cuarta ministra Hola soy taira y yo soy
the Minister of Youth and
la ministra de juventud y tiempo
Leisure And finally, the fifth minister
libre Y por último al quinto ministro o
Hello Hello my
ministra o ministre Hola Hello my
friends, I am the Minister of
Friends yo soy la ministra de
Food if you want to get
alimentación si os queréis poner más
fatter contact me and
gordic os contactá conmigo y más
thinner and thinner Well also or
delgados y más delgados Pues también o
something a diet
algo una dieta
[Music]
[Música]
Hello everyone welcome one more day today I
Hola a todos bienvenidos un día más hoy
'm going to show you How to do makeup like a
os voy a enseñar Cómo maquillar como un
hater it's
hater es
[Music]
[Música]
super easy there you have seen how
superfácil ya está habéis visto qué
easy even a fool can do it UPS
fácil hasta un tonto puede hacerlo UPS
I buy some land as I'm not a
Yo compro una tierra como no soy un
first-class Thai citizen I can't
ciudadano tailandés de primera yo no
own land, since I can't put
puedo tener tierra yo al no poder poner
the land in my name, obviously I
la tierra a mi nombre pues obviamente la
put it in my ex-wife's name with the
pongo a nombre de mi exmujer con el
agreement that obviously as soon as the
acuerdo de que obviamente en cuanto los
children are older I'll try to put the
niños sean más grandes intentar poner la
house land whatever in
casa tierras lo que sea a nombre de
their names there comes a time when it
ellos llega un momento en el cual se
can be done and suddenly they tell me no
puede hacer y de repente me dicen que no
and they tell me that I have to pay rent
y me dicen que tengo que pagar un alquil
What's up guys Well we're on our
Qué pasa chavales Bueno estamos de
way I'm already on our way to the
camino ya estoy de camino a la Tierra
Promised Land and  You might be wondering What is the
prometida y os preguntaréis Qué es la
promised land Well, it's the land
tierra prometida Pues bueno es la tierra
where we're going to set up the sanctuary
donde vamos a montar el el santuario de
okay and nothing is all this but above
acuerdo y nada es todo esto pero sobre
all I want you to see it from above
todo quiero que lo veáis desde arriba
this is going to be the new
este va a ser el nuevo santuario de
animal sanctuary the only thing I'm looking for is
animales lo único que yo busco es la
peace for the animals for me
tranquilidad para los animales para mí
for my children yes I have taken a piece
para mis hijos sí te he quitado un trozo
of your heart what hurts me is because there are
de corazón lo que me duele Es porque hay
many animals that are going to end up in
muchos animales que van a terminar en
a cage he's asking me for 225,000 but that's
una jaula me está pidiendo 225000 pero
over There's no more, there's no turning back
se acabó Ya no hay ya no hay vuelta de
many of you are wondering How
hoja muchos os estáis preguntando Cómo
can you help us save the
podéis ayudar para que salvemos el
sanctuary we need 40,000
santuario necesitamos 40.000
subscriptions on kck she's a brut she's
suscripciones en kck es una brut es
impossible what the [ __ ] are you doing
impos tú qué [__] haces
here I really appreciate it from the bottom of my
aquí te lo agradezco de verdad y de
heart and I came to look for the door
corazón y vine a buscarme la puerta
every morning
todas las mañanas hombre
crazy man I'm having a terrible time
loco estoy pasando fatal
ch What's up guys Well we're
ch Qué pasa chavales Bueno nos estamos
taking a walk around here by the sanctuary we
dando una vuel por aquí por el santuario
already have the lands it's already done
ya tenemos las tierras ya están hecho
we put all the lands together
hemos puesto todas las tierras juntas
with the three crazy ones these with my wild boar
con las tres locas estas con mi jabal
is now the name of the fox of the society
está ya nombre de zorro de la sociedad
with his brothers and to all of you
con sus hermanos y a todos vosotros
many  Thank you and the sanctuary of
muchísimas gracias y el santuario
freedom will be there for many
libertad va a estar ahí por muchos
years to come. You sit in front and you can't even
años te sientas en frente y ni te
imagine that I'm wearing my prettiest skirt for you.
imaginas que llevo por ti mi falda más
And when I see you throw a crystal
bonita y al verte lanzar uno cristal se
in my
in mis
pupinas. Suddenly you look at me, I smile and
pupinas de pronto me miras sonrío y
sigh. I close my eyes. You
suspiras yo cierro los ojos Tú apartas
look away. I barely breathe. I make myself
la vista apenas respiro me hago
small and I start to cry. Hello, watch the
pequeñita y me pongo aar Hola Mira
h 714 radio newsletter. We're
boletín informativo del h 714 radio
starting the morning with
empezamos la mañana con una noticia
urgent news. Tuesday, October 29th. The AMED has
urgente martes 29 de octubre la amed ha
issued a red alert for heavy
emitido una alerta roja por Fuertes
rains in the Valencian Community,
lluvias en la comunidad valenciana
Murcia, part of the Andalusia region.
murcia parte de la región de Andalucía
The hurricane is expected to cause
se espera que la danana cause
intense rainfall that could lead to
precipitaciones intensas que podían
flooding and rivers overflowing.
provocar inundaciones y desbordamientos
Citizens have been advised to avoid unnecessary travel.
ciudadanos evitar desplazamientos
[Music]
[Música]
This is one of the
innecesarios este es uno de los
car cemeteries in the
cementerios de coches que hay en la
Valencian Community after the flood.
comunidad valenciana después de la riada
In this case, we are in Paiporta and
en este caso estamos en paiporta y
behind this cemetery, people continue to
detrás de este cementerio la gente sigue
rebuild their lives thanks to the
reconstruyendo sus vidas gracias a ese
character of the Valencians, as they say.
carácter de los valencianos como dizo
Our Valencian anthem. Let's
nuestro nuestro himno valenci al seuse
continue with it. I would like  claim
seguimos en ello me gustaría reivindicar
Valencia as a symbol of effort and
Valencia como símbolo de esfuerzo y de
struggle and competitions much encouragement and a
lucha y de competencias mucho ánimo y un
big hug to everyone A kiss everyone with
fuerte abrazo a todos Un beso todos con
Valencia everyone with Valencia everyone with Valencia
Valencia todos con Valencia todos con
everyone with Valencia
Valencia todos con Valencia
[Music]
[Música]
live time don't get out of
viv tiempo no sal de
time see you in the next video
tiempo nos vemos en el siguiente vídeo
guys Okay so far the
chavales Bueno pues hasta aquí el
scoundrel I only have one thing left to say to
ruine Solo me queda decir una cosa a
everyone and no mini pan filan
todo el mundo y no mini pan filan
spirit Santi be happy
espíritu Santi sean felices
damn evil beastly cinema
[__] mal bestial cine
[Music]
[Música]
wait for my signal okay unito
espérate a mi señal vale unito para
back one two three we hold on we hold on
atrás una dos tres aguantamos aguantamos
[Music]
[Música]
there okay come on we continue we don't stop
ahí vale venga seguimos no nos paramos
Let's go recording Not recording No I
Vámonos grabando No grabando No que la
've screwed up with something okay
he cagado con algo vale
now serious eh full throttle
ahora serio eh a tope
serious And me what And me what an idiot with that
serio Y yo qué Y yo que que gilipo con
borrowed car from the one who's going to
el coche ese prestado del que te va a
lend you already two fitness go for it you
prestar ya dos fitness tira para ananda
're
que eres
stupid
tonto
health care soipa man the [ __ ] pig drinking
sanidad soipa tío el [__] cerdo bebiendo
beer on the couch being a pimp now being a
cerveza en el sofá de chulo ahora de
pimp being a pimp and me what about And me what an
chulo de chulo y yo que de qué Y yo que
idiot perfect Perfect perfect
gilipolla perfecto Perfecto perfecto
but listen to me
pero escúchame
[Music]
[Música]
Ready,
preparado
good, always
buenas siempre
V, okay, let's go again, Ah, he bumps a
V vale vamos de nuevo que Ah se choca un
little bit.
poquitito
[Music]
[Música]
Come on, record, record something [ __ ], am,
venga tú graba graba algo de [__] am
like.
como
[Music] Comb your
[Música]
hair. Hey, guys. Does anyone know what
peinarte Oye chavales Alguien sabe qué
happens if you run out of pages in your
pasa si te quedas sin hojas en el
passport? It's for a friend, no, not for
pasaporte es para un amigo no no es para
me. Go rewind. Go rewind. Go rewind.
mí ir rewind ir rewind ir rewind